module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'I don\'t have feeling in about half of my body.', 
    a: 'Adam',
    b: 'James',
    c: 'Jalaliani',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I lived in New Zealand for a year. (1999 - 2000)', 
    a: 'Kendra',
    b: 'John',
    c: 'Carolyn',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'My 3rd Great-Grandfather\'s ghost haunts the Old Louisiana State Capitol building.', 
    a: 'Couv',
    b: 'Libby',
    c: 'Mark',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Both of my thumbs are double jointed.', 
    a: 'Smashley',
    b: 'Mitch',
    c: 'Geoff',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'I once rode a camel to a bedouin tent in the desert.', 
    a: 'Josh P',
    b: 'Libby',
    c: 'Jessica',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I know that Billy stole Becky\'s cat toy.', 
    a: 'Nick',
    b: 'Joe',
    c: 'Tomi',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I have rock climbed Devils Tower.', 
    a: 'Sean',
    b: 'RG',
    c: 'RA',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I punched someone at a punk show and made their nose bleed.', 
    a: 'Smashley',
    b: 'Marcus',
    c: 'Jackie',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'I\'ve only ever (halfway) grown 1 wisdom tooth.', 
    a: 'Elizabeth',
    b: 'TayTae',
    c: 'Billy',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'I had to walkie talkie my co-workers from the toilet, b/c there was a rattlesnake in my bathroom.', 
    a: 'Darice',
    b: 'Glynn',
    c: 'Devon',
    d: 'ChelsB',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];
